<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FinalProject</string>

    <!-- Main Activity Strings -->
    <string name="photo_of_the_day">NASA\'s Photo of the Day</string>
    <string name="image_and_video_button">Image and Video Library</string>
    <string name="asteroid_button">Asteroid Watcher</string>
    <string name="mars_weather_button">Mars Weather</string>

    <!-- Mars Weather Activity Strings -->
    <string name="mars_weather_activity_title"><u>Weather at Elysium Planitia</u></string>
    <string name="sol_text">Sol</string>
    <string name="high_temp">High:</string>
    <string name="avg_temp">Avg:</string>
    <string name="low_temp">Low:</string>
    <string name="degrees_f">°F</string>

    <!-- Image and Video Library Activity Strings -->
    <string name="search_prompt">Search:</string>
    <string name="search_button">Go!</string>
    <string name="media_type">Media Type:</string>
    <string name="search_error">Invalid Search Input!</string>
    <string name="no_search_results">No search results!</string>
    <string name="media_title_label"><u>Title</u></string>
    <string name="media_desc_label"><u>Description</u></string>
    <string name="media_type_label"><u>Media Type</u></string>


    <!-- Display Media Activity Strings -->


    <!-- Scavenger Hunt Strings -->
    <string name="scavenger_hunt">Scavenger Hunt</string>
    <string name="huntText1">For your first scavenger hunt item, check out the current weather on
        mars. For extra learning, search the internet for more information about weather patterns on
        mars and how solar dates differ from the date system that we use on earth.
    </string>
    <string name="huntText2">Now that you have got an idea of the weather up on the red
    planet. Its time to learn about the research nasa is doing at the moment. Open up the image
    and video library and check out some videos about the mars rover!</string>
    <string name="huntText3">Learn about one of the most tragic events in the history of
    the United States space program by finding some information about the challenger disaster.
    Who was affected? Why was the mission being undertaken? What changes were made to make
    spaceflight safer?</string>
    <string name="huntText4">You probably noticed the cool space photo when you opened up the
    app. For a learning experience search the content of the photo. Was the photo of a planet?
    A star? Something else? Where is the object located?</string>
    <string name="huntText5">Can you find a video from the original moon landing? Compare the
    technology and appearance of the space craft with footage of
        a more modern spacecraft landing</string>
    <string name="huntText6">Have you ever seen one of the famous movies about the apollo missions?
    Find some footage from the apollo 11 landing? If you have seen the movies, how does the
    movie compare factually to the actual events?</string>
    <string name="huntText7">What happens in the mission control room is one of the most
    important aspects of a successful space landing. Find some footage of what goes on in the room and
    learn more about the process of launching a rocket into space.</string>
    <string name="huntTitle1">1. Mars Weather</string>
    <string name="huntTitle2">2. Mars Rover</string>
    <string name="huntTitle3">3. Challenger Tragedy</string>
    <string name="huntTitle4">4. Photo of the Day</string>
    <string name="huntTitle5">5. Lunar Landing</string>
    <string name="huntTitle6">6. Apollo 11 Mission</string>
    <string name="huntTitle7">7. Mission Control</string>
    <!-- API Key String -->
    <string name="API_KEY">YJAnaNuLHrKq9uW8cYvNkeAnuBbA6CitHSlShwCp</string>
</resources>
